It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
Today after school?
学校帰りで今日?
picture?
え?
There's someone I want to meet today.
今日会わしたい人いるんだよ
Yeah.
うん
Will you meet me?
会ってくれる?
Yeah.
うん
yeah?
ん?
Yeah.
うん
Are you a little short on money?
ちょっとお金困ってるでしょ?
Is this what you were wearing today?
これ今日着てたんだろ?
It suits you.
似合ってんじゃん
Come on, wait a minute.
おいで、ちょっとじゃあ
what happened?
どうしたの?
Are you the one wearing pants?
パンツの人だろ?
picture?
え?
Turn your back.
後ろ向いてさ
Even if it's interesting?
面白いもんしても?
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Let's do something more interesting, then.
もっと面白いことしようか、じゃあ
Hey.
ねえ
You want to, right?
したいでしょ?
interesting.
面白い
You want money, right?
お金欲しいんでしょ?
money?
お金?
Yeah.
うん
Will you give me money?
お金あげるから?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, shall we go?
じゃあ、行くか
Hey!
おい!
Okay, you can come in.
いいよ、入っていいよ
What is that kid?
なにその子?
Look, look, yes.
ほらほら、はい
Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょ?
It's so cute.
めっちゃかわいいじゃん
picture?
え?
Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょ?
Friends, friends, I'll introduce you.
友達、友達、紹介するから
Hello.
こんにちは
You won't show it, right?
映ってくれないでしょ?
誰?
picture?
え?
Friends, friends.
友達だ、友達
friend.
友達
what?
何?
Was it scary?
怖かった?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
This guy is so kind.
優しいから、こいつ
Isn't it cute?
かわいくない?
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
Isn't it cute?
かわいいでしょ?
Today is fine.
今日、いいよ
what?
何?
Isn't it this morning?
今日朝ねえの?
Okay.
いいよ
I'm going home.
帰るんだ
You want money, right?
お金欲しいでしょ?
picture?
え?
You want it, right?
欲しいでしょ?
I'll give you this.
これあげる
Well, let me play with you.
じゃあ、遊んであげて
Why are you scared?
なんでビビってんの?
You know what you're doing today, right?
今日何してるか分かってんでしょ?
sweet.
甘い
Because you're a liar.
だって嘘つくやろ
It's okay to do it.
やってていいよ
cute.
かわいい
It's cute.
かわいいんだよ
You said you like girls like this, right?
こういう子好きって言ってたでしょ?
I like you, don't you?
好きなんだよな、お前
I want to go home.
帰りたい
picture?
え?
I want to go home.
帰りたい
I'm not going back, I've come this far.
帰んないよ、ここまで来てさ
No way.
やだ
why?
なんで?
No way.
やだ
What is it?
なんでしょ?
good.
いい
I've been doing it for a long time.
ずっとしてる
Just play with me.
遊んでやれって
Where are you going?
どこ行くんだよ
It's okay, it's okay.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん
Well, let me play with you.
じゃあ、遊んであげて
You need money, right?
お金必要なんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
Right?
でしょ?
Okay.
いいよ
No way.
やだ
Let's play, come on.
遊ぼうよ、ほら
So, wait.
だから、待ってって
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
It's okay, that's why.
大丈夫、だから
I'll be nice to you.
優しくしてやるからさ
I really want to see it.
めっちゃ見ちゃうな
Okay, okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ、いいよ
This guy is surprisingly erotic.
こいつ、意外にエロいんだよ
This guy is so erotic.
こいつ、エロいんだよ
That's erotic.
エロいな
Let me play with mine too.
俺のも遊ばせてやろう
No way.
やだ
why?
なんで?
I didn't hate it, until just now.
嫌がってなかった、さっきまで
No way.
やだ
There's a strange sound coming out.
なんか、変な声出てるよ
Do what feels good.
気持ちいいことしろよ
No way.
やだ
Are you angry?
怒らしてるんだろ?
Oh no, I hear it's a role.
やだ、役と聞くよ
Isn't this guy erotic?
こいつ、エロいでしょ?
You don't use it.
使わないのね
Nero is also falling.
ネロも落ちてきてる
It's zero.
ゼロいんだよ
It's boring.
おつぶらな
You must be sweating.
汗かいてんじゃないか
Yes, I guess so.
うん、だってんじゃないか
A good body is also quite nice.
いい体も結構いいんだよ
It's going to be dangerous.
やばいしちゃう
Better come to the ass.
お尻に来た方がいい
My stomach is getting bigger.
お腹が大きくしてる
My stomach is getting warm.
お腹が温まってきてる
Don't go this way.
こっちへ行けな
Stick your butt out more.
もっと突き出すんだよ、お尻を
Go this way, come this way.
こっちへ行けよ、こっちへ
Breathe.
息をしてね
You can listen.
お前、聞けんだよ
It's a different voice than before.
さっきと違う声出てるんだよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
No?
やだ?
There aren't many anymore.
もう少なくて
Are you feeling something?
何か感じてんのかな?
Spread it out yourself.
自分で広げてほら
Spread it out quickly, here.
早く広げろ、ほら
Try spreading it out.
広げてみて
Can you see anything?
何か見える?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Does each person show it that way?
一人一人そう見せるの?
Say you don't like it.
嫌とか言って
Do you like Koji Liner?
小事ライナー好きなんだ?
Just lick it, lick it.
ちょっと舐めろ、舐めろ
Spread your legs wider.
もっと足広げろ
I'll be kind to you.
優しくしてあげるから
The person who is licking it will see it properly.
舐めてる人がちゃんと見るんだぞ
I can't spread my legs at all
全く足広げないんだ
Yo.
よ
Try it yourself.
自 分でやってみろ
Over there.
そっち
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
気持ちいいんだね
Show me your pants.
自分でパンツ見せて
I was standing, standing.
立ってたんだ、立って
Can you show me your pants?
パンツ見せてごらん?
Squat down like a tray.
トレイみたいにしゃがんで
Squat down and let your hips go.
しゃがんで腰を離してもらおう
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Make yourself feel good.
気持ちよくして
nice.
いいね
I came here to do something
いっちなことしに来たんだ
reactor.
ろ
Take your time.
じ っくりやるんだぞ
before adding.
加える前に
Lick around.
周りを舐めて
After all, it's about being a person.
やっぱり人にするんだ
Not yet.
まだだぞ
Do you want to lick it?
舐めたいのか?
Do it by hand.
手でやるって
If you lick it, lick it.
舐めたら、舐める
Would you like to lick it?
舐 めて ごらん?
Put your shoes on your cinch.
チェンチに、靴もかけて
You can't do this.
こうやっちゃダメだぞ
Drink sparingly.
まめらに飲む
Drink it up.
飲み上げて
From bottom to top.
下から上に
I guess you like Cenchi.
チェンチに好きなんだろ
Grab your hand.
手掴む
While looking at me.
こっち見ながらな
I like it.
好きなんだよ